<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://murugantemple.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://murugantemple.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pooja Booking and Services Request</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/services-request-later-reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/services-request-later-reference/</guid>
      <description>Use this form below for requesting services that are available online. Please note that we are only listing services that can be performed and requested online in the form below. Some of the services not listed below requires you to be at the temple (example - Kaavidi or Palkudam). For a list of all available services, please visit the link here. Payment is handled by PayPal.
If there is a service that is not listed, please make a general donation for the total amount and contact the temple with your PayPal transaction to notify of any details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pooja Booking and Services Request</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/services-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/services-request/</guid>
      <description>Use this form below for requesting services that are available online. Please note that we are only listing services that can be performed and requested online in the form below. Some of the services not listed below requires you to be at the temple (example - Kaavidi or Palkudam). For a list of all available services, please visit the link here. Payment is handled by PayPal.
If there is a service that is not listed, please make a general donation for the total amount and contact the temple with your PayPal transaction to notify of any details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arohara : An E-Concert Series Presented By Murugan Temple of North America</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/events/arohara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/events/arohara/</guid>
      <description>AROHARA in an E-concert series organized by MTNA. This is a free concert series, however we welcome your donations at this difficult time where we all are affected. Your donations are tax-deductible. Donations could be made through the below PAYPAL link. Thank you for your continuous support to YOUR Murugan TempleDonation Amount: $Checkout With PayPal --Watch Arohara vol 3 Live Concert On YouTube Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arohara : An E-Concert Series Presented By Murugan Temple of North America</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/events/arohara4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/events/arohara4/</guid>
      <description>AROHARA in an E-concert series organized by MTNA. This is a free concert series, however we welcome your donations at this difficult time where we all are affected. Your donations are tax-deductible. Donations could be made through the below PAYPAL link. Thank you for your continuous support to YOUR Murugan TempleDonation Amount: $Checkout With PayPal --Watch Arohara vol 4 Live Concert On YouTube Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PayPal Issues</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/paypal-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/paypal-issues/</guid>
      <description>My PayPal payment is not working?
If your PayPal payment is not working it could be due to a variety of reasons. If you have clicked &#34;Checkout with PayPal&#34; and nothing happens or you only see a blank window, then you most likely have a pop-up blocker installed. This pop-up blocker will block PayPal from opening an additional payment window. So all you need to do is temporarily disable it and then the window can open or load properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Ways To Give To Muruga</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-give/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-give/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for visiting this page. Murugan Temple depends on your support and contributions. Here are many ways through which you can provide your support. Some of them such as the Amazon Smile requires no effort on your part but to simply designate &#34;Murugan Temple&#34; as the charity you support. Please go through them and provide us your support.
Amazon Smile ProgramMake a difference with each purchase on AmazonWhen you shop on Amazon, simply use &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murugan Temple : Check-In Forms and Process For Visiting Temple</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/checkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/checkin/</guid>
      <description>Murugan Temple Now Open (With Limited Access)
SCROLL DOWN FOR THE FORM
The rules, timings and procedures are in place for your own safety and the safety of others at the temple.
PLEASE READ, UNDERSTAND AND RESPECT THE RULES!Thank You.
Temple ScheduleThe temple will follow the following schedule:
The temple is closed to the public until further notice.
Please note that all poojas will be performed daily and telecasted on Facebook Live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deepavali Sweets 2020</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/diwali-sweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/diwali-sweets/</guid>
      <description>Order in Advance - WhatsApp a temple volunteer at (732) 421-3154. PLEASE DO NOT CALL. PLEASE USE WHATSAPP MESSAGING!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murugan Temple Virtual Tour</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-virtualtour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-virtualtour/</guid>
      <description>தமிழால் இணைவோம் முருகன் அருள் பெறுவோம்Thank You Arthi Prem for sharing this video on YouTube.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murugan Temple : Additional Instructions</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/additional-instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/additional-instructions/</guid>
      <description>Dear Devotees:
As your wellbeing is our utmost priority, for past couple of months, we temporarily closed the Murugan Temple for the public. Now, as the COVID-19 cases are declining in our area, we believe it is time to provide LIMITED ACCESS for devotees to the temple. We plan to open the temple to devotees from Wednesday, July 15, 2020. Your safety is our primary objective; so, we will enforce the following precautionary measures:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Donation</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/monthly-donation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/monthly-donation/</guid>
      <description>
Options to Consider:
Option #1: You can setup a monthly donation through your bank by filling out the ACH form here
Option #2: You can visit &#34;Donate Online&#34; and you will be directed to PayPal. There you can setup a monthly contribution. We thank you on behalf of Murugan Temple. May Lord Murga bless you and your family with an abundance of wealth and happiness!
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate Towards Projects At Murugan Temple</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/donate-towards-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/donate-towards-projects/</guid>
      <description>At Murugan Temple, you can make a donation towards one or more of the following projects. All contributions/donations are fully tax deductable. Please add the items to the cart and then check-out the cart when you&#39;re ready to proceed to the payment screen. Thank you.List of ProjectsCovid Relief FundAmount: $Add to CartSilver Kavasam Project (for Navagraham)Total Project Cost: $15,000Amount: $Add to CartShopping Cart Details:Total: Checkout via PayPalClear CartsimpleCart({checkout: { type: &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate Online</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/donate-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/donate-online/</guid>
      <description>Murugan Temple uses both PayPal and Zelle for accepting online donations in a secure manner. If you are donating less than $1000, please click the &#34;Donate Now via PayPal&#34; (green-button) below to be redirected to PayPal where you can specify the amount you wish to donate and complete the transaction. (NOTE: There are no transactions fees on the donor side. The temple incurs a transaction fee on the receiving side).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple Management</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/administration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:39:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/administration/</guid>
      <description>Our Board of Trustees  Dr. Guruswamy Gopal - Chairman Mr. Gnanavel Munirathinam - Secretary Mrs. Nagulam Loganathan Mr. Rotter Jeyakumar Mariampillai Mrs. Shobana Mylvaganam Mr. Ganayswaran Nathan Dr. Kalpana Ramiah Mrs. Puwaneswari Sachitanandan Dr. Mouna Selvam Mrs. Inpah Siva  To reach the board, send email to mtnaboard@gmail.com
The contact details has not been shown above to protect the privacy of the individuals. To contact the Trustees of the Board, please call the temple at (301) 552-4889 and talk to the temple manager requesting the information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Murugan Temple</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-temple/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-temple/</guid>
      <description>தமிழால் இணைவோம் முருகன் அருள் பெறுவோம்The history and development of Murugan Temple of North America is a fascinating and simultaneously heart-warming experience for those who have been involved since its inception. It is a story to be told, read and preserved for posterity. It is the story that reflects the glory of Lord Murugan and His immeasurable blessings to all His devotees, wherever they may live and worship him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childrens School &amp; Education</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/childrens-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/childrens-school/</guid>
      <description>Class Schedule As Follows:
Classes are conducted on 2nd and 4th Sunday’s of each month from September to June
10:15am – 11:15am ....... Tamil Class11:15am – 11:45am ....... Bhajan Class11:45am – 12:30am ....... Hinduism Class12:30am – 1:00am ....... Yoga ClassFor enrollment details contact:
Pathmathevan Mahadevan at appan69&amp;#64;h&amp;#111;&amp;#116;mai&amp;#108;&amp;#46;c&amp;#111;mVayudeva Varadan at v&amp;#97;yud&amp;#101;va&amp;#64;ea&amp;#114;thl&amp;#105;&amp;#110;k&amp;#46;netWe look forward to seeing you and your child at the Murugan Temple Children’s Class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID Relief Efforts by MTNA</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/covid-relief-effort/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/covid-relief-effort/</guid>
      <description>COVID Relief EffortsMurugan Temple is coordinating a Covid Relief Fund. You could donate generously towards the cause. All contributions/donations are fully tax deductible. Please add the items to the cart and then check-out the cart when you&#39;re ready to proceed to the payment screen. Thank you.Arohara #8 is targeted towards raising funds to Covid-Relief in Sri Lanka. As you may have heard and seen on the news, Sri Lanka is very badly affected due to the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murugan Temple Endowment Fund</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/endowment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/endowment/</guid>
      <description>Murugan Temple of North America Endowment FundWhat is an Endowment?
An endowment is any asset donated to and for the perpetual (everlasting) benefit of a non-profit organization. The donation is usually made with the requirement that the principal remain intact and money earned from investing the principal be used for a specific purpose. Endowment creates an ongoing source of income and provides Growth, Financial Safety and Stability to the organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murugan Temple Volunteers</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/volunteers/</guid>
      <description>Murugan Temple is run by volunteers like you. You can join our global community of volunteers by simply contacting the coordinator listed below.Our volunteer activities includes:GeneralAdministrationCultural committeeFund Raising ActivitiesFinance committeeFront-Desk managementGarland and PujaFood and KitchenNewsletter committeeLibrary (Thiru Muruga Kirupanandha Variyar Swamy Library)Religious activities and preparationTemple BeautificationWebsite SupportYouth Activities and EducationInfrastructure MaintenanceGardening and Outside BeautificationPublic Relations committeeFund Raising ActivitiesSound, Music System, Stage Lighting EngineerNetworking EngineerTelephony SupportSquare Register SupportNot finding an activity of interest in the list above, then simple come by the temple on a weekend and helps us in whatever capacity you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pooja Booking and Services Request</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/services-request-prev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/services-request-prev/</guid>
      <description>Use this form below for requesting services that are available online. Please note that we are only listing services that can be performed and requested online in the form below. Some of the services not listed below requires you to be at the temple (example - Kaavidi or Palkudam). For a list of all available services, please visit the link here. Payment is handled by PayPal.
If there is a service that is not listed, please make a general donation for the total amount and contact the temple with your PayPal transaction to notify of any details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religious Services</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/our-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/our-services/</guid>
      <description>Pooja Booking &amp;amp; Services Request
Click on &amp;ldquo;Pooja Booking &amp;amp; Services Request&amp;rdquo; for requesting your online services.
The following are among the services that will be provided at the Temple or at Devotees’ residences as appropriate, upon request. Devotees are urged to make prior arrangements by calling the Temple in advance to make reservations and to ascertain that priests will be available to perform these special requests. Appropriate charge for the services including Sambhavanai for the priests will be payable to the temple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple Auditorium Rental</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-auditorium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/about-auditorium/</guid>
      <description>The auditorium with a capacity of 200 is available for rent for family functions such as wedding, naming ceremony, arangetram, seemantham etc., and community events. The stage, state-of-the-art sound system, high-end stage lighting, tables and chairs are included in the rental. This facility has private dressing rooms and rest-rooms. The temple has brand new kitchen and can order food for your events from our kitchen.
Manager manages all bookings for Temple Auditorium, special Temple ceremonies, and Priest’s time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year-End Tax/Contribution Statement</title>
      <link>http://murugantemple.org/about/year-end-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 19:38:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://murugantemple.org/about/year-end-statement/</guid>
      <description>How do we accept donations?There are four methods through which Murugan Temple accepts donations:Cash-Donations - receipt is provided at the templeBank Cheques - receipt is provided at the temple or the check-transaction through your bank is the proof of paymentSquare Payments at Temple (using your credit-cards) - individual receipts and statements*1 will be available at SquareUp.com PayPal Payments via Temple Website - individual receipts and statements*1 will be available at PayPal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
